#### Contact

lockwood.melissa@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/melissa-lockwood-4291a267 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Safety
Hospitals

### Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Professional Working)

### Certifications

Family Nurse Practitioner (FNP)
Critical Care Registered Nurse
(CCNS)
ACLS/BLS
PALS

# Melissa Lockwood

FNP-C, MSN, CCRN

Greater Denver Area

## Summary

Ready to work and relocate to Denver-Boulder area. Medically bilingual FNP-C with extensive experience as a registered nurse and a demonstrated history of working in the emergency, trauma, and critical care specialties of the health care industry. Expert in management of adult and pediatric patients with Congenital Heart Disease. Skilled in Extra-Corporeal Membrane Oxygenation Life Support, Patient Education and Health Prevention, Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR), and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Excellent and proven interpersonal customer service skills. Healthcare services professional with a Bachelor of Science (BS) in Nursing degree from Stephen F. Austin State University and a Master of Science in Nursing degree from Walden University.

#readytowork

## Experience

Texas Children's Hospital Registered Nurse August 2016 - Present (3 years 11 months) Houston, Texas

Trinity Air Ambulance International Flight Nurse
July 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 1 month)
Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Memorial Regional Hospital Registered Nurse II July 2014 - July 2016 (2 years 1 month) Hollywood, FL

Good Shepherd Health System

3 years 3 months

Registered Nurse

January 2012 - July 2014 (2 years 7 months)

Nurse Extern

May 2011 - January 2012 (9 months)

## Education

Walden University

Master of Science - MS, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2017 - 2019)

Stephen F. Austin State University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2009 - 2011)

Louisiana State University in Shreveport

Bachelor of Science (BS), Molecular Biology · (2005 - 2009)